[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Hosni Mubarak"]}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "What do you think is the most credible in terms of the status of Hosni Mubarak's health?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "is", "the", "most", "credible", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "status", "of", "Hosni", "Mubarak", "'s", "health", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Well, Piers, I don't think there's any question that Hosni Mubarak's health took a turn for the worst today.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "'s", "any", "question", "that", "Hosni", "Mubarak", "'s", "health", "took", "a", "turn", "for", "the", "worst", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hosni Mubarak"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "It is frankly in chaos, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "frankly", "in", "chaos", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "I wouldn't call it chaos.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "call", "it", "chaos", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Fran, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Fran", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "I'm good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "So the president made this big speech tonight.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "the", "president", "made", "this", "big", "speech", "tonight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "What did you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Well, he's talking about that -- the thing that was in the German newspaper.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "talking", "about", "that", "--", "the", "thing", "that", "was", "in", "the", "German", "newspaper", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VB", "TO", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Do they appreciate it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "appreciate", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "I think they do and I think what he was trying to do with his time at the microphone was say to people, I don't have control over everything.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "do", "and", "I", "think", "what", "he", "was", "trying", "to", "do", "with", "his", "time", "at", "the", "microphone", "was", "say", "to", "people", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "control", "over", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "What should world leaders be talking to each other about actually doing to stop that sense of dangling on the precipice?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "world", "leaders", "be", "talking", "to", "each", "other", "about", "actually", "doing", "to", "stop", "that", "sense", "of", "dangling", "on", "the", "precipice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well, whether we're talking about the future of the euro and all of these governments that need bailouts, whether we're talking about our own problem with entitlements getting so expensive, and the ballooning deficits and debt, I mean, what we need to do is look five and 10 years down the road and make decisions that are responsible for the future and not just expedient for us right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "whether", "we", "'re", "talking", "about", "the", "future", "of", "the", "euro", "and", "all", "of", "these", "governments", "that", "need", "bailouts", ",", "whether", "we", "'re", "talking", "about", "our", "own", "problem", "with", "entitlements", "getting", "so", "expensive", ",", "and", "the", "ballooning", "deficits", "and", "debt", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "what", "we", "need", "to", "do", "is", "look", "five", "and", "10", "years", "down", "the", "road", "and", "make", "decisions", "that", "are", "responsible", "for", "the", "future", "and", "not", "just", "expedient", "for", "us", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "He's being a bit more playful, but more -- dare I say human?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "being", "a", "bit", "more", "playful", ",", "but", "more", "--", "dare", "I", "say", "human", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RBR", ":", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Is this going to be a really aggressive tightly forged contest, you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "going", "to", "be", "a", "really", "aggressive", "tightly", "forged", "contest", ",", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marco Rubio"]}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Would he be the kind of choice, if you were Mitt Romney, that you would go for?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "he", "be", "the", "kind", "of", "choice", ",", "if", "you", "were", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "that", "you", "would", "go", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "I'm going out on a limb and tell you, I'm pretty sure Marco Rubio will not the choice.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "out", "on", "a", "limb", "and", "tell", "you", ",", "I", "'m", "pretty", "sure", "Marco", "Rubio", "will", "not", "the", "choice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Is it in the end they may not be vote winners for President Obama even though many would believe they're the right thing to do?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "in", "the", "end", "they", "may", "not", "be", "vote", "winners", "for", "President", "Obama", "even", "though", "many", "would", "believe", "they", "'re", "the", "right", "thing", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Well, the question about those hot issues is, in all of those cases you were going through, you're basically identifying some of his strongest constituencies of voters.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "question", "about", "those", "hot", "issues", "is", ",", "in", "all", "of", "those", "cases", "you", "were", "going", "through", ",", "you", "'re", "basically", "identifying", "some", "of", "his", "strongest", "constituencies", "of", "voters", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Is it \"Days of Our Lives\"?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "``", "Days", "of", "Our", "Lives", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "``", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "I think it's \"General Hospital.\"", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "``", "General", "Hospital", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "It's not really a laughing matter, this, is it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "really", "a", "laughing", "matter", ",", "this", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "No, I absolutely agree.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "absolutely", "agree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "Based on what happened today, what is your take on her involvement?", "question_tokens": ["Based", "on", "what", "happened", "today", ",", "what", "is", "your", "take", "on", "her", "involvement", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "Well, I think, you know, she probably is, as she presented, a sweet old lady.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", ",", "you", "know", ",", "she", "probably", "is", ",", "as", "she", "presented", ",", "a", "sweet", "old", "lady", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Is there a danger if you go too hard, you alienate a jury?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "danger", "if", "you", "go", "too", "hard", ",", "you", "alienate", "a", "jury", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Am I wrong?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Well, personality disorder are real and pervasive, but at the end of the day, if you look at him, he had a relationship with his wife for 46 years.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "personality", "disorder", "are", "real", "and", "pervasive", ",", "but", "at", "the", "end", "of", "the", "day", ",", "if", "you", "look", "at", "him", ",", "he", "had", "a", "relationship", "with", "his", "wife", "for", "46", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Have you ever heard of this in all your time working in the sex crimes area?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "heard", "of", "this", "in", "all", "your", "time", "working", "in", "the", "sex", "crimes", "area", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "I had never heard of it, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "never", "heard", "of", "it", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "But certainly when you hear that for the first time, as I did last night, you are shocked, because it appears to be a confession, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "certainly", "when", "you", "hear", "that", "for", "the", "first", "time", ",", "as", "I", "did", "last", "night", ",", "you", "are", "shocked", ",", "because", "it", "appears", "to", "be", "a", "confession", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Well, it sounds incriminating.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "sounds", "incriminating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Would you do that if you were in that position now?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "do", "that", "if", "you", "were", "in", "that", "position", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Well, I think it depends how they've seen the says go in.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "depends", "how", "they", "'ve", "seen", "the", "says", "go", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "If President Obama says he's the right guy to be elected in November, has he earned that right from the way that he's conducted himself economically?", "question_tokens": ["If", "President", "Obama", "says", "he", "'s", "the", "right", "guy", "to", "be", "elected", "in", "November", ",", "has", "he", "earned", "that", "right", "from", "the", "way", "that", "he", "'s", "conducted", "himself", "economically", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Well, I think he said something in a speech the other day that was very telling.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "said", "something", "in", "a", "speech", "the", "other", "day", "that", "was", "very", "telling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "In your lifetime, have you ever seen a worse situation for the American economy than the one that we're currently in?", "question_tokens": ["In", "your", "lifetime", ",", "have", "you", "ever", "seen", "a", "worse", "situation", "for", "the", "American", "economy", "than", "the", "one", "that", "we", "'re", "currently", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Yeah, I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Were you agreeing with him or not?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "agreeing", "with", "him", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "No, I was arguing about that.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "was", "arguing", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "In other words, how much does personal responsibility play here?", "question_tokens": ["In", "other", "words", ",", "how", "much", "does", "personal", "responsibility", "play", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "The vast majority of it.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "vast", "majority", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Michele?", "question_tokens": ["Michele", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Hi.", "answer_tokens": ["Hi", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "And then secondly, when exactly do you start giving to charity?", "question_tokens": ["And", "then", "secondly", ",", "when", "exactly", "do", "you", "start", "giving", "to", "charity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Well, I would give always off the top before you do anything else.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "give", "always", "off", "the", "top", "before", "you", "do", "anything", "else", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "Michele, are you satisfied with that?", "question_tokens": ["Michele", ",", "are", "you", "satisfied", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Yeah, that's great.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "that", "'s", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Or would you like a different kind of attitude?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "would", "you", "like", "a", "different", "kind", "of", "attitude", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Well, that lady has fallen prey to a false set of logic.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "lady", "has", "fallen", "prey", "to", "a", "false", "set", "of", "logic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "Are you an Obama man at heart?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "an", "Obama", "man", "at", "heart", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120619pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "What is the kind of leader that you're craving in an American president?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "kind", "of", "leader", "that", "you", "'re", "craving", "in", "an", "American", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "Moral compass.", "answer_tokens": ["Moral", "compass", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]